《迷失》前情提要
Previously on "lost"...
不管Ben Linus在兰花站里做了什么
whatever ben linus did down at the orchid station,
都可能把我们隔离了
It may have... dislodged us.
这座岛穿越时空了吗
The island is moving through time?
可能是岛  也可能是我们
Yeah, either the island is, or we are.
我要你回到牛津大学
I need you to go back to oxford university.
回到我们相见的地方
Go back to where we met!
在那里找到我妈  她叫...
I need you to go there and find my mother! her name is--
你没事吧
Are you all right?
-我刚在岛上  -你已经离开岛上三年了
I was on the island. you've been off the island for three years.
你现在安然无恙  只是个梦而已
You're safe now. it was just a dream.
Pen  我不是在做梦
It wasn't a dream, pen.
是段记忆
It was a memory.
Efren Salonga
Efren salonga?
Ef-efren salonga!
Efren Salonga
Efren salonga?
Efren salonga!
Efren Salonga
Efren salonga?
你是谁
Who are you?
你就是那个医生吗
Are you the doctor?
对
Yes.
你怎么了
What's the matter with you?
知道该做什么吗
You're sure you know what you're doing, yeah?
-当然  -因为她留了很多血
- Yes, yes! - Because there's a lot of blood, man!
-留了多少血  -Penny  我来了
- How much blood? - I'm coming, penny!
Pan  没事的  找到医生了
It's okay, pen. we've got a doctor.
你去哪里了
Where have you been?!
会好的  会好的  好  躺好
It's gonna be okay. it's gonna be okay. okay, here you go.
深呼吸  Penny  深呼吸
Okay. just breathe, penny, okay? j-just breathe.
深呼吸
Oh! breathe.
-我气透不上来  -你做得很好
- I can't breathe. - You're doing great. you're doing great, okay.
坚强点
Okay, just be strong, yeah? okay.
-快让孩子出来  -坚强点
- Make it come out. - Please be strong.
坚持住  坚持住
Hold it. hold it.
我不行
I can't!
你可以的  Penny
Yes, you-- yes, you can, penny.
用力  用力
Push! push!
现在用力  Penny  用力
Okay, push now, penny. push. now!
加油  Penny  快出来了
Come on, penny. that's it. it's coming.
再用点力  Penny  用力
Push harder! come on, penny. push!
我看见小脑袋了!
I can see the head! I can see the head!
-在来一次  用力  -就快出来了
- One more time! push! - I can see it. it's just coming.
出来了  出来了
It's coming! it'coming!
你做到了
You did it.
Penny  你做到了
Oh, my god, penny. you did it.
是个男孩
It's a boy.
我爱你  Penny  我爱你
I love you, penny. I love you.
他真漂亮
Oh, oh, he's beautiful. beautiful.
天呐  他好帅啊
Oh, my god. he's so beautiful.
天呐
Oh, my god.
我爱你
I love you.
看
Look.
就在那边
Right out there.
在你看不见的地方  有一座岛
Beyond where you can see, there's--there's an island,
一座非常特别的岛
And it's a very special island.
我很久以前离开了那里
I left it a long time ago.
从没想过我会再见到它
I never thought I'd see it again.
它叫英国
It's called great britain.
那座岛屿最美的地方是苏格兰
And the most beautiful part of the island is scotland,
那也是你爸爸的出身地
And that's where your daddy's from.
那里有山脉  幽谷  还有深湖的水怪
There's mountains and glens and monsters in deep lochs,
还有
And...
那也是你爸爸妈妈
And it's where your mommy and daddy...
想恋的地方
Fell in love.
也是她心碎的地方
It's also where he broke her heart.
我...
Yeah, well, i...
我以为你会忘记那段往事
I thought I'd leave that wee bit out of it.
你也漏说了他的爷爷
You also left out the bit about his grandfather--
他派了艘船去岛上
The man who sent a boat to the island
去将爸爸的朋友赶尽杀绝
To kill all daddy's friends.
我们来去自由  他永远不会知道我们在这里
We'll be in and out. he'll never know we're here, penny.
别小看他  Desmond
Don't underestimate him, desmond.
如果他知道我们在这里  不知他会怎么做
If he finds out we're here, I don't know what he'll do.
可这与你的父亲无关  Penny
But this has nothing to do with your father, penny.
我们是因为Daniel Faraday才来到这里
We are here because of daniel faraday.
他告诉我
What he told me--
岛上的每个人都身处险境
That everyone on that island is in danger,
我是唯一能帮他们的人
And I am the only one that can help them.
我不得不这么做  Penny
I have to do this, penny.
你确定他是这么说的吗
Are you sure that's what he said?
Sawyer说在那条小溪会合
Yeah, sawyer said to meet at the creek,
如果他被射死了
So unless he got torched by a flaming arrow,
那就是他要其他人去的地方
That's where he and everyone else should be.
你的头痛怎么样了
Hey, how's your headache?
更严重了
Worse, actually.
可考虑到我们在为生存而奔波
But considering we're running for our lives,
我不会发牢骚
I'm not gonna complain.
你有没有头昏眼花或看见重影
You have any dizziness or double vision?
都有
Both, actually.
为什么你那么担忧
Why do you look so worried?
你是不是知道我会出什么事
Is it because you know what's happening to me?
你不会有事的
Listen to me. nothing is gonna happen to you. nothing.
有我在
I won't let it.
我们到了
Hey, we're here!
只有我们到了这里
Some rendezvous. it's just us.
我们该等等
Well, we should probably wait, see if they show up.
没准他们就在后面
They could be right behind us.
-是呀  他们没准来过  -没准死了
- Yeah, or they came and left. or they're dead.
Miles  你的那种态度
Miles, that right there, that kind of attitude...
得改一改
Not exactly what we need right now.
大家已经够害怕了  Miles
People are scared enough as it is. miles--
Miles
Miles?
停下  别动
Wait! don't move! aah!
你们谁是头
Who's in charge here?
他
He is.
你非得来是吧
You just couldn't stay away, could you?
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： 非燕    daisy静    牛牛    rosemaryai
翻译： buffy小朋友   字幕总监：非燕
■
时间轴： 非燕  夏小山    校对：  许愿
他吃完早饭了吗
Did he finish his breakfast?
吃完了
Yeah.
开始不听话  不过还是乖乖顺从了
Gave me a bit of a fight, but he listens in the end...
不像他爸爸
Unlike his father.
听着亲爱的
Look, honey,
我只要找到他妈妈
All I have to do is find his mother,
告诉她他还在岛上
Tell her he's still on the island,
-然后就彻底结束  -为何现在
- And then I'm done with this for good.  - why now?
如果他在岛上就告诉了你一切
I mean, if he told you all this on the island,
你怎么会两天前才想起
Why didn't you remember it until two days ago?
我不知道
I don't know.
这其中道理  我了解的
Look, I don't understand how any of this works
并不比你多
Any more than you do. it...
我就是知道这发生了
Look, I know it happened.
Daniel Faraday敲开了舱门
Daniel faraday knocked on the hatch door
告诉我去牛津
And told me to go to oxford...
所有人都有危险
Everyone was in danger,
而我是唯一可以救他们的人
And I was the only one that could save them.
我知道这听起来很疯狂
I know how insane it sounds.
我会在天黑前回来
I'll be back by dark,
然后一切结束
And then I'm done...
永不再提
Forever.
我保证
I promise.
如果你要保证什么  Des
If you're gonna promise me something, des,
能保证你再不回那岛了吗
Can you promise me you'll never go back to that island again?
我干嘛再回那岛
Why in god's name would I ever go back there?
海滩上你们还有20个人,但这只有5个人
There were 20 of you at the beach, But only five of you here.
其他人呢
Where are the rest of your people?
也许被你的其他陷阱炸死了
Maybe they got blown up by some more of your land mines.
那不是我们放的  是你放的
We didn't put them here. you did.
离开这里后
Once we leave here,
你就不归我管了
I will be out of control of what happens to you.
但若你现在合作一切会容易很多
But if you cooperate now, Things will go much easier for you.
告诉我其他人在那里
So where are the rest of your people?
我不知道
I don't know.
这些人是谁
Who are these people?
我还没空问,当时情况紧急
Well, gee, I didn't have time to ask that, With frogurt on fire and all.
他们在海滩上袭击我们
They attacked us on the beach.
这是一支30口径格兰德步枪  很新
This is a 30-caliber m1 garand rifle. it looks new.
管什么步枪  你去哪里了
Who cares about the rifle? where the hell you been?
要是你有了我的经历  James
If you've been going through what I have, james,
也许就会更恰当的问
Maybe the more appropriate question would be,
我去什么时间了
When the hell have I been?
-你的腿怎么回事  -被射中了
- What happened to your leg?  - I got shot.
-谁干的  -过会儿再聊吧
- By who?  - we can swap stories later.
我们和其他人说好要在溪边见
We told the rest of our group that we would meet them at the creek.
如果还想和他们联系上就得出发了
If there's any chance Of reconnecting with them, we'd better get moving.
既然我们没有绳子绑住他们
Fine, seeing as we have no rope
以防我们再被袭击
To make sure these two don't try to kill us again.
-我们只能打死他们  -[拉丁语]
- Guess we're gonna have to shoot 'em.  - quare non sunt vestitus eis?
-[拉丁语]  -什么
- Tace!  - what?
-那是什么语言  -他们在说拉丁语
- What kind of language is that?  - they're speaking latin.
一个问我们怎么没穿制服
That one asked why we aren't in uniform,
另一个叫他闭嘴
And this one told him to shut up.
他们怎么会懂拉丁语  Juliet
And how is it that they know how to speak latin, juliet?
和我一样
The same reason I do.
他们是"The Others"
Because they're others.
-听着  -什么
- Hey.  - yeah.
-我们刚走过一个新坟  -什么
- We just walked over a fresh grave.  - what?
四个美国大兵
Four u.s. soldiers,
刚死一个月
Dead just under a month.
三个被打死
Three of them were shot.
一个辐射致死
One died of radiation poisoning.
Miles  听着
Miles, hey, hey.
有没有哪个提到这是几几年
Did any of them happen to mention what year it is?
我们到了
We're here.
Richard  我们回来了
Richard? we're back.
在溪边抓住三个
Caught the three by the creek.
这个是他们的头
This one's their leader.
你叫什么
What's your name?
我叫Richard Alpert
My name is Richard Alpert.
我想你是回来找炸弹的
I assume you've come back for your bomb.
抱歉,先生,我没找到Faraday的记录
No, I'm sorry, sir. I'm not find a record of any faraday.
这不可能
No, that--that's impossible.
我知道她儿子在这做教授
'cause I know her son was a professor here.
他叫Daniel Faraday  他肯定有记录
His name's Daniel Faraday. I'm sure he's in your database.
先生,没有任何关于Faraday被牛津雇佣的记录
Sir, there's no record of any Faraday Ever having been employed here at oxford.
我去看过他
I visited him.
我去了他的实验室  在阁楼里
I went to his lab. it was in an attic.
在物理系楼上
It was...  it was above the physics department.
档案记录很久了,可能是写错了
The archives go back quite far. Perhaps there was a clerical error.
能回忆一下,你最后一次拜访是哪一年吗
You don't happen to recall the year In which you last visited?
哪一年
The year?
不  我
No. I'm...
我不确定
I'm not exactly sure.
能问下你为什么查这条信息吗
May I ask why you're seeking this information?
抱歉  麻烦你了
Sorry I wasted your time.
别碰它
Yeah, I wouldn't touch that.
就知道有人会知道...
I wondered when someone'd figure out
我们不是在消毒
Were weren't just fumigating here.
你是教授
You a professor?
不算是
No. not exactly.
至少你还诚实
At least you're honest.
为什么让我不要碰它
So why'd you tell me not to touch it?
我是来把这些恶心的老鼠
Because I'm the one who had to take the rats that he made
扔进焚尸炉的人
Run through this bloody thing down to the incinerator
-这样就没人知道他都做了什么  -你是说Daniel Faraday
So that no one would find out what he was up to. you mean daniel faraday.
是啊,你不是唯一打听..他和他的工作的人
Yeah. you're not the first one to poke around here, asking about him and his work.
传言说他曾经试图让老鼠穿越时空
Rumor had it, he was trying to send rats' brains back in time.
真可笑  对吗
Ridiculous, innit?
是啊
Aye.
只要你和别人讲...
Look, I'll forget you broke my lock
这些都是一个疯子留下的垃圾
If you tell your mates that all you found
我就不计较你闯进来了
Was rubbish left behind by a madman.
好的
Fair enough.
Faraday
Faraday--
学校说没有关于他的记录
The university says there's no record of him.
你能责备他们吗
Well, can you blame 'em?
在他对那可怜姑娘做了那些事以后
I mean, after what he'd done to that poor girl?
什么女孩
What girl?
小心
Hey, take it easy.
Dan  我没事
It's all right, dan. I'm fine.
我们会死的
We are so dead.
不
Hey. no, no, no.
我们会没事的
We are not so dead. we're gonna be fine.
直到下一次闪光  我们要在一起
We just need to keep it together until there's another flash.
然后这些就都消失了
All right? then all this disappears.
-什么时候  -可能五分钟后
And when's that gonna happen? could be five minutes.
也可能5000年后
Could also be 5,000 years.
太好了
That's--that's just awesome.
怎么回事  Dan
What is going on, dan?
-为什么他们这样对我们  -我不知道
Why are they doing this to us? I'm not sure.
他们肯定认为我们是美军的人
But they must think that we're with the american military.
如果是这样  我们活着的唯一机会
And if that's the case, our best chance of staying alive
就是让他们一直这样想  让...
Is to let them keep thinking it, all right? let--
对不起  打搅你们了吗
Sorry. am I interrupting?
Ellie告诉我你们不愿意说出其他人在哪
Ellie tells me that you're not willing to reveal Where the rest your squad is.
我为什么说  这样你们会也杀了他们
And why would I do that? so you can kill them, too?
我们没这样做  朋友  你们的人袭击了我们
We didn't start this, friend. your people attacked us.
你们来我们的小岛做试验
You come to our island to run your tests,
向我们开枪
You fire on us, and what,
还想我们不要保卫自己的家园
You expect us notto defend ourselves?
我不知道这些事  我们是科学家
I don't know anything about that. we are scientists.
那又怎么样  他们派你们来找回它吗
So what? so they sent you here to recover it?
你说的是说氢弹吧
If you mean our hydrogen bomb, then yes.
从他的辐射伤势我猜
And I'm guessing from this man's radiation burns
这间房子已经遭到了辐射
That the housing has been compromised.
对吗
Is that right?
听我说
You need to listen to me.
这个装置极不稳定
You have an unstable device
有可能会毁了整个小岛
That's capable of destroying this entire island,
它发生了故障
And it's broken.
如果你不让我使它停下来
If you don't allow me to render it inert,
我们都会死
All of us are gonna die.
所有人  我怎么知道你不是来执行自杀任务的
All of us. how do I know you weren't sent here on some suicide mission?
我带你去炸弹那里
That I'll take you out to the bomb,
然后你把它引爆
And you'll just detonate it?
因为...
Because...
因为我爱坐在我旁边的这个女人
I'm in love with the woman sitting next to me.
我永远不会...
And I would never...
我永远也不会做伤害她的事
I'd never do anything to hurt her.
好吧
All right.
修好你的炸弹
Take care of your bomb.
不过如果你想做什么事   都会伤害到她
But you try anything else, and you will hurt her.
谁教的你拉丁语
So who taught you latin?
我们必修的
Others 101.
启蒙的语言嘛
Gotta learn latin-- language of the enlightened.
去你的启蒙
Enlightened, my ass.
我建议你跟我们谈谈
I suggest you talk to us.
要是等我们回到小溪
Once we get back to the creek
跟其他人汇合
And meet up with the rest of our people,
会有很多人对你弄气冲冲
There's gonna be a lot of anger directed at you
剩下的人有的被抓了
For attacking them. the rest of your people
-有的死了  -什么
Are either captured or dead. what?
为什么这么说
What makes you say that?
那个白痴大喊"小溪那见"
That idiot shouted out, "meet at the creek."
我们知道他们要去哪
We knew exactly where they were headed.
派人跟着他们
Sent a group after them.
或许我可以用我的暗语说  James  等等
Well, maybe I should've said it in my secret language. james, wait.
我们不是你们的敌人
We're not your enemy
那就放了我们
then let us go
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you sayin'?
带我们去你们的营地
take us to your camp
带我们去
please
我为什么带你们去
why would i do that
是不是
is
Richard在那
...Richard there?
Richard Alpert
Richard Alpert?
你刚才说"Richard Alpert"
Did you just say "richard alpert"?
John  拜托
John, please.
带我们去你们的营地
bring us to your camp
没人会死
no one else has to die
带我们去
please
好吧
All right.
向东走两公里
Okay, we need to head east another couple of kilometers
直到那座山...
Unl we hit the ridge--
开枪
Shoot him!
开枪  该死的
Shoot, damn it!
你疯了吗  想什么呢
Are you crazy?! what were you thinking?
你怎么不向他开枪
Why didn't you shoot him?!
因为
Because...
他是我的人
He's one of my people.
你是谁
And who might you be?
我叫Desmond Hume  我找Theresa Spencer
Uh, my name's desmond hume. I'm looking for Theresa Spencer.
我是Abigail Spencer  Theresa的姐姐
I'm Abigail Spencer. Theresa's my sister.
我可以和她谈一下吗
Oh, right. um, can I have a word with her?
你要和Theresa谈话
You wanna speak to Theresa?
我在牛津大学碰到一位先生
Yeah, I got her name
是从他那里得到她的名字
From a-a gentleman I met at oxford university--
那位先生叫Daniel Faraday
Um... Daniel Faraday.
Daniel Faraday
Daniel Faraday?
你怎么不早说
Well, why didn't you say so?
请吧  请进
Please, you must come in.
谢谢
Thanks.
他没告诉你  是吗
He didn't tell you, did he?
没有  他没告诉我
No. no, he didn't.
她能听见我们说话吗
Can she hear us?
不能  Theresa现在离开了
No. Theresa's away right now.
"离开"  什么意思
"away"? what do you mean?
有时她醒来  认为自己只有三岁
Well, sometimes she wakes up, thinks she's 3,
想要知道她的洋娃娃在哪儿
Wants to know where her dolly is.
昨天  她和我们的爸爸说话
Yesterday, she was talking to our dad.
而他五年前就死了
He died five years ago.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
肯定是搞错了  我不应该来的
Um, this was a mistake. i... I shouldn't have come.
当然
Of course.
你怎么会想留下来
Why would you want to stay?
Daniel一定不会
Daniel certainly didn't.
他就这样弃她于不顾
He left her like this?
逃到美国去  再也没有音信
Went running off to the states, never to be heard from again.
他抛弃了她
He abandoned her.
哪种人会这么干
What kind of a man does that?
如果不是Widmore先生
I seriously don't know what we would've done
我真的不知道他做了什么
If it hadn't been for mr. widmore.
对不起  谁
Uh, I'm sorry. who?
Daniel的资助人
Daniel's benefactor.
他资助他的研究
He funded his research,
而他为此结果负责
And he took responsibility for the result of it.
自从Theresa开始这样起  他就照顾她
He's been taking care of Theresa ever since this happened to her.
这儿的一切都多亏Widmore先生
Everything here is due to Mr. Widmore,
上帝保佑他
God bless him.
氢弹
A hydrogen bomb?
真的吗
Seriously?
回溯到50年代
Back in the '50s,
美国政府在南太平洋试验氢弹
The U.S. government tested h-bombs in the south pacific.
我们真走运
Lucky us.
你不必那么说
You didn't have to say that.
说什么
Say what?
说你爱我
That you loved me.
有很多其他的借口
I mean, there are plenty of other ways
你可以用来说服他
You could've convinced him
你不会把整个岛都炸掉
You weren't gonna blow up the entire island.
我这么说
I said what I said
因为我就是这个意思  Charlotte
Because I meant it, Charlotte.
行了
Right, then.
我们走
Let's go.
我保证  很快回来
Back soon. I promise.
不管你的上级跟你说了什么
Whatever your, uh, your superiors told you,
我想要你知道真相
I want you to know the truth.
一个月以前  我们发现了一个营的18名成员
A month ago, we found 18 members of an army battalion
就在我们的丛林  架起了这座帐篷
Right here in our jungle here, setting up this camp.
我们给了他们离开此岛的机会
We gave them the opportunity to leave the island peacefully.
他们不愿意那么做  所以我被迫杀了他们
They weren't willing to do that, so I was forced to kill 'em.
全部
All of 'em.
-被迫  -是的
- Forced? - Yeah.
谁下的命令
By whom?
你对某人负责  不是吗
Y-you answer to someone, don't you?
遵循一系列的命令  对吧
You follow a chain of command, right?
-是的  -我也是
- Yeah. - yeah, well, so do i.
Richard  Richard
Richard! Richard!
你到底怎么了
What the hell happened to you?
Cunningham和我  他们突袭了我们
Cunningham and i-- a group of them surprised us.
我们寡不敌众  但是我逃掉了
We were outnumbered, but I escaped.
-寡不敌众  -闭嘴  Ellie
- Outnumbered, eh? - Shut up, Ellie.
-他是谁  -他会帮我们解决问题
- Who's this? - He's gonna help us take care of our problem.
-你最好开始行动  -他是他们中的一员
- You'd better get going. - Wait. he's one of them.
你不能信任他
You can't actually trust him.
行了  你听到我说的了  Ellie  去吧
Yeah, you heard me, Ellie. go.
-你是怎么逃脱的  -跑啊
- H-how did you escape? - I ran.
你没想过他们会跟踪你吗
And it never occurred to you that they might follow you?
跟踪我  他们的头儿是个下贱的老头
Follow me? Their leader is some sodding old man.
你认为他能追踪到我
What, you think he can track me?
你认为他比我更了解这个岛
You think he knows this island better than I do?
你怎么知道Richard会到这里来
How did you know Richard would be here?
Richard一直在这儿
Richard's always been here.
他多大
How old is he?
一把年纪了
Old.
John  你为什么对Richard那么感兴趣
Why are you so interested in Richard, John?
我对他感兴趣
I'm interested in him
是因为他可能告诉我该怎么拯救我们
Because he was about to tell me how I could save us.
拯救我们
"save us"?
是的
Yeah.
但是在他说完之前
But before he could finish,
我们就被闪光打断了
We were interrupted by that flash of light.
-我希望还能继续下去  -我不想打断
- And I'm hoping we can pick up where we left off. - I hate to bust up
你们自己人的重聚
The "i'm an other, you're an other" reunion,
Faraday  那个确实能拯救我们的家伙
But Faraday--the guy that's actually gonna save us--
快被拖进丛林被枪毙了
Is being death marched into the jungle right now.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
你不准备帮我救他吗
You're not gonna help me save him?
不  我准备过去
No.I'm gonna go down
了结我和Richard的谈话
finish my conversation with richard.
那会害死我们的
That's gonna get us all killed.
你过去后他们就知道我们在这了
You go rolling in there, they're gonna know we're here.
我会先给你10分钟跑路的
Fair enough. I'll give you ten minutes head start.
那你呢
What about you?
你想留在这个疯城里
You wanna stay here in crazytown
还是帮我救那个书呆子
Or help me rescue the geek?
你为什么一直看着我
Why do you keep looking at me?
不  我不是  我
No, no, I'm--i'm not. i--
你是的
You are.
你知道吗  你是对的  对不起
You know what? you're right. I'm--i'm sorry.
只是
It's just...
你看起来很像
You look so much like...
我认识的一个人
Someone I used to know.
不是那个
Someone other than the girl
你疯狂地爱着的女孩吧
you just professed your love for?
-难道你是罗密欧吗  -不是的  相信我
- Well, aren't you the romeo.  - far from it, believe me.
我不信你
I don't believe you, by the way.
你也许蒙过Richard了
You may have richard fooled,
但是你别指望我会信你
You can't really expect me to believe
你  一个英国人  一个中国人
That you, a british woman and a chinese man
都是美国军队的成员
Are all members of the united states military.
你们是谁
Who are you
你们在岛上干什么
And what are you doing on our island?
你想知道我是谁
You wanna know who I am?
我是你拆除那个炸弹的
I'm your best chance
唯一希望
At disarming that bomb.
就在那里
Right, then,
拆除它
Disarm it.
你在那里做什么
What are you doing up there?
我在检查
I'm examining it.
-退后  -什么
- Back up. - What?
退后  退后
Get back, get back.
这不安全  我们得离开
It's unsafe. we need to move.
我发誓  如果你试图
I swear, if you try anything...
如果我试图干什么
If I try anything--
你就会  你就会打死我
What, you're gonna-- you're gonna shoot me?
是吗
Is that right?
好了  这好极了  因为  毫无疑问
Yeah, that would be perfect because, of course,
来复枪的火力正在  你管这个叫什么
Rifle fire right next to-- what would you call this--
氢弹的附近  是的  真是异想天开
Hydrogen bomb? yes, fantastic idea.
真的会引爆氢弹
Really... inspired.
好了  听我说
Okay, listen to me.
-你的人有办法找到铅或混凝土吗  -干什么
- Do you people have any access to lead or concrete? - for what?
外箱上有一道裂痕  需要铅来填补
There's a crack in the casing. it needs to be filled with lead.
需要很小心地把它从平台上拿下来
You need to take it off this platform carefully
-埋了它  -你绕了这么大一个圈子
- And bury it. - You brought me all the way out here
就是为了告诉我们得埋了它
To tell us that we have to bury it?
你告诉Alpert你可以拆除那东西
You told Alpert you could disarm that thing.
无需担心,照我说的做,埋了它,它不会爆炸的
You don't need to worry. You do what I say, you bury it, it won't go off.
-你怎么知道  -你得相信我
- How do you know that? - I need you to trust me.
我不相信你
I don't trust you.
只要埋了它  就什么事都没有
just bury it. bury it, and everything will be fine.
你的长官命令我来处理这件事
Remember, your superior ordered me to take care of this.
你怎么能这么确定
How can you be so sure?
你要处理这个炸弹吗  那就埋了它
You wanna take care of this bomb? you bury it!
你怎么知道不会有事
How?! how do you know that?
因为50年后  这个岛还存在
Because 50 years from now, this island is still here!
你
There you...
你说的是什么
What did you just say?
别紧张
Whoa. take it easy.
我可以解释得更清楚些
I can explain myself a little better.
我知道这听起来怪异
I know how this sounds.
相信我  这很难解释
Believe me, it's... oh, it's hard to explain.
50年后
50 years from now,
我和我的
Me and my..
我和我的朋友
Me and my friends--
我们就是从那里来的
That's where we're from, okay?
关键在这儿  一切都安好
And here's the key-- everything's fine.
我不是说非常完美
I'm not saying it's perfectly fine,
但是没有原子弹爆炸
But there hasn't been any atomic blasts, all right?
把枪发下  金发女郎
There has not-- drop the gun, blondie.
没事
It's okay.
你可以把枪发下
She's okay. you can put your gun down.
她先放下
She puts hers down first.
为什么我们不都放下抢
Why don't we all put our guns down?
我说  放下枪
I said, drop it!
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
他们也来自未来吗
Are they from the future, too?
你告诉她了
You told her?
先生  你不能
Sir! sir, you can't--
Widwore先生
Mr. widmore.
对不起  他没经过我就进来了
I'm so sorry. he charged right past me.
没事  Melanie
That's all right, melanie.
Hume先生是...我的是一个同事
Mr. hume is a... colleague of mine.
让我们单独谈谈
Please leave us.
我知道你有问题问我
I know you have questions for me.
我不会回答的
I'm not gonna answer them.
我来这是想问你点事
I've come here to ask you something.
只要你告诉我想知道的
And once you've told me everything I need to know,
我永远都不再来找你
You'll never see me again.
明白吗
Understand?
好的
All right.
我想知道Daniel Faraday的母亲在哪
I need to know where I can find daniel faraday's mother.
你怎么知道我能回答你
What makes you think I would even know the answer to that?
因为在你把Faraday放到那船上
Because even before you put faraday on your little boat
送到小岛上之前
And sent him off to the island,
你已经资助他的研究十年之久
You spent ten years funding his research.
所有我想你肯定知道点什么
So I figure, you must know something
关于他的近亲
Regarding his next of kin.
Desmond
我有三年没有任何关于我女儿的消息了
I haven't seen or heard from my daughter for three years.
只要回答我
Just answer me this.
她安全吗
Is she safe?
Faradey的妈妈在哪
Where's faraday's mother?
她在洛杉矶
She's in los angeles.
这是她的地址
This is an address for her.
她不会很乐意见你的
I suspect she won't be pleased to see you.
她比较喜欢独处
She's a very private person.
等等  Desmond
Wait, desmond.
把你的信息传到...
Deliver your message...
然后就不要管这个烂摊子了
But then get out of this mess.
不要让Penny有危险
Don't put penny's life in danger.
危险
Danger?
很多很多年以前
You're getting yourself involved in something
你就让自己介入了某件事
That goes back many, many years.
但是这都与你和我女儿无关
It has nothing to do with you or my daughter.
不管你们俩躲在哪
Wherever you were hiding...
回去吧
Go back there.
谢谢你的建议
Thanks for the advice.
Richard Alpert
Richard alpert!
-我在找Richard  -别动
- I'm looking for richard.  - don't move.
-Richard Alpert  -跪下  快
- Richard alpert!  - on the ground now.
Richard  我有事要跟你说
Richard, I need to talk to you!
闭上你的嘴
Shut your mouth!
够了
That's enough!
你是谁
Who are you?
我的名字是John Locke
My name is john locke.
那对我来说应该有什么意义吗
Is that supposed to mean something to me?
Jacob派我来的
Jacob sent me.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
什么
What?
Richard  你不会真的信他吧
Richard, you can't seriously trust him.
我说了...把枪放下  Widmore
I said... put the gun down, widmore.
你叫	Widmore
Your name is widmore?
Charles Widmore
Charles widmore?
关你什么事
What's it to you?
没什么  很高兴见到你
Nothing. it's... nice to meet you.
但是它看到了熊  所以它逃跑了
But it saw the bear so that it ran away again.
哪里
Where?
今天过的不错吧
Good day?
是啊
Yeah.
他想去泰晤士河钓鱼
He wanted to go fishing in the thames.
我们没成功
We were unsuccessful.
你呢
And you?
你找到Faradey的母亲了吗
Did you find faraday's mum?
不用找了
there was no one to find.
她几年前就去世了
She, um...She died a few years ago.
你为什么骗我
Why are you lying to me?
什么  我没有啊
What? I'm not.
她在哪里
Where is she?
她在洛杉矶
She's in los angeles.
Pen  你没什么好担心的
Look, pen, you've got nothing to worry about.
你知道  这都是一个错误
You know, this was a mistake.
不  我承诺这些一天之内都能办好的
No, i... I made a promise that this would be done in a day
现在办好了  这已经不是我们的问题了
And now it's done. it's not our problem anymore.
要是你明天醒来
And what happens if you wake up tomorrow
-又记起别的什么了呢  -那我就忘掉
- And remember something else?  - then I'll forget it.
-还有后天呢  -我会忘掉的
- And the next day?  - I'll forget it.
这都不重要  Pen
It doesn't matter, pen.
你们才是我的生活全部  你和Charlie
You're my life now-- you and charlie.
我不会再丢下你的
I won't leave you again...
不会因为这个
Not for this...
不会为了任何事
Not for anything.
你永远都忘不了的  Des
You'll never forget it, des.
所以我想我们得跟你一起去
So I guess we're going with you.
我给你这个的吗
I gave you this?
是的
Yes.
在你腿上中枪之后
After you were shot in the leg
然后我...从丛林里走出来帮你处理伤口
And i... wandered out of the jungle to patch you up?
是的
That's right.
那我为什么什么都不记得...任何细节
Then why don't I remember... well, any of this?
因为这些都还未发生呢
Because it hasn't happened yet.
我不知道你希望我说什么  John Locke
I'm not sure what you're expecting me to say, john locke.
我期望你告诉我怎么离开这个岛
I expect you to tell me how to get off the island.
那是高度机密
That's very privileged information.
我为什么要告诉你
Why would I share it with you?
因为你告诉我
Because you told me that
一旦我到了这里
I had something very impornt to do
有很重要的事需要我完成
Once I get there.
还有因为我是你的头儿
And because I'm your leader.
-你是我的头儿  -你是这么告诉我的
- You're my leader?  - that's what you told me.
我不想自我矛盾
Look, i... certainly don't want to contradict myself,
但是...关于选择头儿
But... we have a very specific process
我们有个具体程序要走
For selecting our leadership,
而且这在很小的年纪就要开始了
And it starts at a very, very young age.
好吧  好吧
All right. all right.
现在是几几年
What year is it right now?
1954年
It's 1954.
1956年  3月30日  2年以后
All right. may 30, 1956-- 2 years from now--
是我出生的日子
That's the day I'm born--
加州的塔斯廷   如果你不信我
Tustin, california, and if you don't believe me,
我建议你自己去看看
I suggest you come and visit me.
不
Oh, no.
-怎么了  -又要发生了
- What's wrong?  - it's about to happen again.
你现在就得告诉我  Richard
You need to tell me now, richard.
我要怎么离开这个岛  拜托  告诉我
How do I get off the island? please! tell me!
我想是的
I think so
Charlotte
你没事吧
You okay
是  我没事
Yeah I'm fine.
我也是诶
Yeah,me too.
Charlotte
看着我  看着我  没事的
Look at me,look at me.It's ok.
没事的
It's ok
Charlotte